Arthur Espartinez



artespar85@gmail.com



09155979561



linkedin.com/in/arthur-espartinez-a2b1ba218



https://arthurespartinez25.github.io/portfolio/

Summary

I would like to contribute to your organization as a full-stack developer, leveraging my ability to develop E-commerce web applications using readily available-web applications. With my passion for learning, I will be able to take part in empowering your team with my newly found coding experience.

Experience

Research And Development Engineer

AWS Philippines (Advanced World Systems, Inc. and Advanced World Solutions, Inc.)

Nov 2021 - Present (9 months +)

- -Created inventory system using C language.
- -Training in MERN Stack, Angular, Java

Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 (2 months)

Capstone Project 1 - Static Website

- Created a static personal portfolio website
- Used HTML, CSS and Javacscript
- Hosted using Github

Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 (2 months)

Capstone Project 2 - E-commerce API Development

- Created an API development of an e-commerce using Express.js, Node.js and MongoDB with the following functionalities:
- a. User registration and authentication
- b. Admin authorization
- c. Creating of orders
- Hosted using Heroku

Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 (2 months)

Capstone Project 3 - Full-Stack Website

- Created e-commerce website using MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js)
- Created the frontend application using React.JS
- Created the backend server using Express.JS, Node.JS and MongoDB as database

- Hosted using Vercel and Heroku

Mall Manager

LAMVER CONSOLIDATED COMPLEX DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION

Jun 2019 - Feb 2020 (9 months)

Service Advisor

Inframachineries Corporation

Nov 2017 - Jan 2019 (1 year 3 months)

After-sales service and maintenance engineer on heavy equipment like excavator and loader

Education

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Postgraduate/ Certificate Course, Web Development

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021

Attended an 8-week full time web development training at Zuitt Coding Bootcamp in a live online format. I learned how to create static web apps, a backend application supporting its interactive web app, and an understanding of client and server interaction.

Bicol University

Bachelor's degree, Mechanical Engineering Jun 2013 - Apr 2017

Licenses & Certifications



Mechanical Engineer - Bicol University

Issued Nov 2017 - Expires Jan 2023

Skills

Front-end Development • Back-End Web Development • Full-Stack Development • Lead Generation • Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • Web Development • Adobe Photoshop • WordPress • Microsoft Office • Microsoft Excel